http://www.pricksofthetrade.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy for Investus Inc
Skip to contentTOLL FREE: 1-888-944-8841 (Mon - Fri, 8AM to 4PM)|support@tattoomachineequipment.comBLOG
Shipping & FAQ
My Account Remember MeRegister
Quality Tattoo Supplies for Professionals
Search for:
Tattoo Supplies
Art & Stencil SuppliesMachine Accessories & PartsInk Cups & HoldersFurniture & DisplayTubes, Grips & TipsBottles & ContainersDisposable GlovesCarrying Cases & BagsShop ToolsTattoo Medical Supplies
Skin PreparationSterilization ProductsAftercareAnestheticsDisposable GlovesWorkstationTattoo Machines
Tattoo PensUnion MachinesCheyenneStigma RotaryJavelin Tattoo PenDickie GoldenGolden Tattoo MachineJack SteelSabre RotaryMicky BeeFeldmanDiablo Kami RotaryDiablo Slide RotaryStorm RotaryBorgIron Inx CustomsHildbrandtPittsburg IronsTTS MachinesRotary MachinesInkstar MachinesMachine PartsPower Supply
Clip Cords & Foot PedalsM-NINE Electric BikeJuul Compatible DeviceTattoo Needles
Tattoo Needle CartridgesFor CheyenneTubes, Grips & TipsStainless Steel Tattoo GripsTattoo Ink
IntenzeBoris HungaryDragon ColorsMario Gold LabelMark MahoneyMike DeMasiBob TyrrellBlacks, Outlining and GraywashInk SetsRadiant ColorsDynamic ColorsMOMs MillenniumStarbrite ColorsKuro Sumi ColorsKuro Sumi Outlining & ShadingVictor Portugal BG Shading Tattoo Ink SetsBlacks, Outlining, Shading & WashesUV BlacklightTattoo Ink SetsEducation
Tattoo Kits
Coil KitsTattoo Pen KitsRotary KitsClearanceTattoo Supplies
Art & Stencil SuppliesMachine Accessories & PartsInk Cups & HoldersFurniture & DisplayTubes, Grips & TipsBottles & ContainersDisposable GlovesCarrying Cases & BagsShop ToolsTattoo Medical Supplies
Skin PreparationSterilization ProductsAftercareAnestheticsDisposable GlovesWorkstationTattoo Machines
Tattoo PensUnion MachinesCheyenneStigma RotaryJavelin Tattoo PenDickie GoldenGolden Tattoo MachineJack SteelSabre RotaryMicky BeeFeldmanDiablo Kami RotaryDiablo Slide RotaryStorm RotaryBorgIron Inx CustomsHildbrandtPittsburg IronsTTS MachinesRotary MachinesInkstar MachinesMachine PartsPower Supply
Clip Cords & Foot PedalsM-NINE Electric BikeJuul Compatible DeviceTattoo Needles
Tattoo Needle CartridgesFor CheyenneTubes, Grips & TipsStainless Steel Tattoo GripsTattoo Ink
IntenzeBoris HungaryDragon ColorsMario Gold LabelMark MahoneyMike DeMasiBob TyrrellBlacks, Outlining and GraywashInk SetsRadiant ColorsDynamic ColorsMOMs MillenniumStarbrite ColorsKuro Sumi ColorsKuro Sumi Outlining & ShadingVictor Portugal BG Shading Tattoo Ink SetsBlacks, Outlining, Shading & WashesUV BlacklightTattoo Ink SetsEducation
Tattoo Kits
Coil KitsTattoo Pen KitsRotary KitsClearance Search for:
Privacy Policy Privacy PolicyRICHARD FONG2018-07-16T03:50:40-07:00Privacy Policy For Investus IncOperating Hildbrandt Tattoo Supply Information CollectionWe collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, or email subscription for promotional newsletters. When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously as well. Like many websites, we use “cookies” to enhance user experience and gather information about our visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the “Do we use ‘cookies’?” section below for information about cookies and how we use them.How do we use your information?We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, email subscription for promotional newsletters or use certain other site features in the following ways:To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.To quickly process your transactions.If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please refer to the “How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?” section below. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and ‘members-only’ content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us.How do we protect visitor information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.Do we use “cookies”?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won’t have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service at 1 888 944 8841.Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information except as described below. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety.However, that information will not include any personal or financial payment information.How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?To modify your e-mail subscriptions, please just opt out with the easy opt out link in our emails.To delete all of your online account information from our database, sign into the “My Account” section of our site and remove your shipping addresses and billing addresses. Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for required record keeping.Third party linksIn an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).Changes to our policyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on January 26, 2017Questions and feedbackWe welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue. You can contact us at 1 888 944 8841 or email: support@tattoomachineequipment.comOnline Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Terms and ConditionsPlease also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.Your consentBy using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. support@tattoomachineequipment.com For Canadian orders we ship from our warehouse in Richmond BC.For United States orders, we ship via our shipping office in Point Roberts WA.We also service international orders and have shipped products to over 50 countries worldwide.Our head office is located in Richmond BC Canada.3871 North Fraser Way, Unit 2 Burnaby BC V5J5G6Order Toll-Free 1-888-944-8841FOLLOW US
hildbrandtEst. 2006, Hildbrandt has been supplying the tattoo industry for over a decade! DM/email us photos of your work for a feature & discount code.
Thank you @tattooarteporvida for sharing his beaut
To all our beloved customers, we are moving to 2-3
A beautiful leopard piece by @kyrainks. Thank you
The Immortal Line Portable Tattoo Power Supply is
Load More...
©
Investus Inc. | Privacy Policy | Site Map | Terms & Conditions | WordPress Web Design by Graphically Speaking
